{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856148105","data":{"timestamp":" 947856148104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 6f7fbe04-ddb5-493c-a472-f4135c8a24a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856160390","data":{"timestamp":" 947856160389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856163412","data":{"timestamp":" 947856163411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856166372","data":{"timestamp":" 947856166372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856169523","data":{"timestamp":" 947856169522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856172639","data":{"timestamp":" 947856172639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856175676","data":{"timestamp":" 947856175676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856178223","data":{"timestamp":" 947856178222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856181350","data":{"timestamp":" 947856181349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856184332","data":{"timestamp":" 947856184331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856187374","data":{"timestamp":" 947856187373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856191067","data":{"timestamp":" 947856191067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856191122","data":{"timestamp":" 947856191122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856233570","data":{"timestamp":" 947856233569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" f960e318-4604-40da-8960-0bbf0dea112a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856257585","data":{"timestamp":" 947856257585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856264210","data":{"timestamp":" 947856264210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856271741","data":{"timestamp":" 947856271740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856282459","data":{"timestamp":" 947856282459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856289083","data":{"timestamp":" 947856289083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856296606","data":{"timestamp":" 947856296606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856307240","data":{"timestamp":" 947856307237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856313427","data":{"timestamp":" 947856313427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856320848","data":{"timestamp":" 947856320848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856331477","data":{"timestamp":" 947856331477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856338085","data":{"timestamp":" 947856338084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856345610","data":{"timestamp":" 947856345609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856356272","data":{"timestamp":" 947856356272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856362893","data":{"timestamp":" 947856362892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856369504","data":{"timestamp":" 947856369504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856376111","data":{"timestamp":" 947856376111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856382736","data":{"timestamp":" 947856382736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856390161","data":{"timestamp":" 947856390161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856400759","data":{"timestamp":" 947856400759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856409737","data":{"timestamp":" 947856409736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856417629","data":{"timestamp":" 947856417629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" ff6a5c31-294d-4a99-9aec-7b00a0a7a92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856438747","data":{"timestamp":" 947856438747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856445354","data":{"timestamp":" 947856445354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856451963","data":{"timestamp":" 947856451963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856458568","data":{"timestamp":" 947856458568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856465976","data":{"timestamp":" 947856465976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856472583","data":{"timestamp":" 947856472582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856480025","data":{"timestamp":" 947856480025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856486632","data":{"timestamp":" 947856486632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856494091","data":{"timestamp":" 947856494091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856504705","data":{"timestamp":" 947856504705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856511312","data":{"timestamp":" 947856511311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856518737","data":{"timestamp":" 947856518737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856529418","data":{"timestamp":" 947856529418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856536014","data":{"timestamp":" 947856536014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856543437","data":{"timestamp":" 947856543437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856550027","data":{"timestamp":" 947856550027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856556635","data":{"timestamp":" 947856556635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856564062","data":{"timestamp":" 947856564062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856574744","data":{"timestamp":" 947856574743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856587778","data":{"timestamp":" 947856587778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 2cb8d022-c298-4a2e-a577-dfda6c09d718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856613021","data":{"timestamp":" 947856613021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856619631","data":{"timestamp":" 947856619631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856627187","data":{"timestamp":" 947856627187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856637900","data":{"timestamp":" 947856637900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856644073","data":{"timestamp":" 947856644073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856651501","data":{"timestamp":" 947856651501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856658125","data":{"timestamp":" 947856658125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856665682","data":{"timestamp":" 947856665682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856672289","data":{"timestamp":" 947856672289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856678898","data":{"timestamp":" 947856678897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856686357","data":{"timestamp":" 947856686357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856697038","data":{"timestamp":" 947856697038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856703647","data":{"timestamp":" 947856703646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856710271","data":{"timestamp":" 947856710271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856717733","data":{"timestamp":" 947856717733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856728380","data":{"timestamp":" 947856728379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856734991","data":{"timestamp":" 947856734991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856741599","data":{"timestamp":" 947856741598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856749041","data":{"timestamp":" 947856749041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856757908","data":{"timestamp":" 947856757908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 02510e19-4ddc-42ca-936c-4518add16960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856781006","data":{"timestamp":" 947856781006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856787613","data":{"timestamp":" 947856787612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856794238","data":{"timestamp":" 947856794238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856801665","data":{"timestamp":" 947856801665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856812325","data":{"timestamp":" 947856812324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856818986","data":{"timestamp":" 947856818986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856825593","data":{"timestamp":" 947856825593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856832185","data":{"timestamp":" 947856832185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856839614","data":{"timestamp":" 947856839614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856846204","data":{"timestamp":" 947856846204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856852795","data":{"timestamp":" 947856852795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856859405","data":{"timestamp":" 947856859405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856866035","data":{"timestamp":" 947856866035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856873489","data":{"timestamp":" 947856873489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947856886540","data":{"timestamp":" 947856886540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_162218"," gameId":" 380d1c03-f446-4d57-a159-60c823cf9a0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}